Guide to Major Figures in American Music
Major Figures in American Music
- Woolf, Randall
  - Woolf, Randall, 2005 April 27; OHV 342 a-c; Transcript Page Count: 93 pages
- Wuorinen, Charles
  - Wuorinen, Charles, 1975 July 14; OHV 263 c
    Cole Gagne
  - Wuorinen, Charles, 1983 November 10; OHV 263 h-j
    Wuorinen, Charles, 1938-
  - Wuorinen, Charles, 1985 July 24; OHV 263 g; Approximate Running Time: 60 mins
  - Wuorinen, Charles, 1990 August 10; OHV 263 a-b; Approximate Running Time: 64 mins
  - Wuorinen, Charles, 2002 June 14; OHV 263 d-f; Transcript Page Count: 56 pages
- Wyner, Yehudi
  - Wyner, Yehudi, 1998 October 15 1998 October 16; OHV 290 a-d; Approximate Running Time: 184 mins; Transcript Page Count: 71 pages
    Bellagio, Italy
  - Wyner, Yehudi, 2001 March 29; OHV 290 e-g; Approximate Running Time: 127 mins
  - Wyner, Yehudi, 2004 November 5; OHV 290 h; Transcript Page Count: 45 pages
    Seminar at Northeastern Univ.
  - Wyner, Yehudi, 2011 April 14; OHV 290 i; Approximate Running Time: 85 mins
- Xenakis, Iannis
  - Xenakis, Iannis, 1983 March 1; OHV 360 a; Approximate Running Time: 37 mins
  - Xenakis, Iannis, 1986; OHV 360 b-d; Xenakis, Iannis, 1922-2001
- Yates, Peter
  - Yates, Peter, 1967 January 1; OHV 60 a-d; Transcript Page Count: 194 pages
    Adelaide G. Turner
- Young, La Monte
  - Young, La Monte, 2002 July 11; OHV 327 a-c; Approximate Running Time: 168 mins
- Young, Nina C.
  - Young, Nina C., 2023 April 6; OHV 577 a; 2 Computer Files; 764 megabytes; Approximate running time: 76 mins
    Young, Nina C., 1984-
- Zappa, Frank
  - Zappa, Frank, 1977 August 17; OHV 67 a-c; Transcript Page Count: 68 pages
    David B. Fischer
- Ziporyn, Evan
  - Ziporyn, Evan, 1977 April 1; OHV 270 k; Ziporyn, Evan (1959-)
  - Ziporyn, Evan, 1997 December 9; OHV 270 a-g; Approximate Running Time: 318 mins; Transcript Page Count: 111 pages
  - Ziporyn, Evan, 2006 February 1; OHV 270 h-i; Approximate Running Time: 222 mins
  - Ziporyn, Evan, 2014 April 10; OHV 270 j-k; Approximate Running Time: 74 mins
- Zorn, John
  - Zorn, John, 1990 January 25; OHV 220 a-h; Approximate Running Time: 248 mins; Transcript Page Count: 153 pages
- Z, Pamela
  - Z, Pamela, 2021 January 13; OHV 544 a; 1 Computer File; 2.95 gigabytes; Approximate running time: 242 mins
    Interview conducted via videochat, with interviewee located in San Francisco, CA and interviewer in Guilford, CT.
    Z, Pamela, 1956-
  - Z, Pamela, 2021 March 18; OHV 544 b; 1 Computer File; 637 megabytes; Approximate running time: 70 mins.
- Zwilich, Ellen Taaffe
  - Zwilich, Ellen Taaffe, 1984 May 18; OHV 177 c; Approximate Running Time: 43 mins; Transcript Page Count: 9 pages
  - Zwilich, Ellen Taaffe, 1985 May 29; OHV 177 j; Approximate Running Time: 65 mins
  - Zwilich, Ellen Taaffe, 1986 October 1; OHV 177 a-b; Approximate Running Time: 88 mins; Transcript Page Count: 30 pages
  - Zwilich, Ellen Taaffe, 1989 October 2; OHV 177 d-e; Approximate Running Time: 68 mins
  - Zwilich, Ellen Taaffe, 1989 October 3; OHV v177 R1-2
  - Zwilich, Ellen Taaffe, 1990 September 7; OHV 177 f; Approximate Running Time: 42 mins
  - Zwilich, Ellen Taaffe, 2002 October 24; OHV 177 g-i; Approximate Running Time: 93 mins; Transcript Page Count: 32 pages
  - Zwilich, Ellen Taaffe, 2008 April 3; OHV 177 k; Approximate Running Time: 59 mins
  - Zwilich, Ellen Taaffe, 2018 November 1; OHV 177 l; Approximate Running Time: 46 mins